Everyone's out to get them... If they don't kill each other first.
The Hitman's Bodyguard is a action, comedy, crime
film directed by Patrick Hughes.
The world’s top bodyguard gets a new client, a hitman who must
testify at the International Court of Justice.
They must put their differences aside and work
together to make it to the trial on time.
Michael Bryce, played by Ryan Reynolds.
Darius Kincaid, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Vladislav Dukhovich, played by Gary Oldman.
Sonia Kincaid, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Amelia Roussel, played by Élodie Yung.
Seifert, played by Richard E. Grant.
The Hitman's Bodyguard is a 2017 action comedy film directed
by Patrick Hughes and written by Tom O'Connor.
It stars Ryan Reynolds, Samuel L.
Jackson, Gary Oldman and Salma Hayek.
In the film, Michael Bryce (Reynolds) must protect Darius Kincaid (Jackson), an imprisoned hitman on his way to testify at
the International Criminal Court against a sadistic Eastern European dictator Vladislav Dukhovich (Oldman).
The Hitman's Bodyguard was released in the United States on 18
August 2017 and grossed $183 million worldwide.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised its performances, action sequences, and the
chemistry between Reynolds and Jackson, but criticized its plot and execution.
A sequel titled Hitman's Wife's Bodyguard was released on 16 June 2021.
The film explores themes of assassin, court, england, hitman, bodyguard.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.